Bhavesh Shahani

JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

Pangalore,India.

gudd.shahani@gmail.com

in BhaveshShahani LinkedIn

BhaveshShahani_Github

▶ BhaveshShahani_Portfolio



PROFESSIONAL SUMMERY

Software Developer with knowledge of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Able to learn new technologies and software. Have an experience of 1000+ hours of Coding and Data Structure Algorithms. Team player who provides valuable support in a team environment.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer

Masai School Apr 2022 – Present | Bangalore

Senior Secondary Education

Sanmati School May 2016 | Indore

CERTIFICATES

Diploma In Event Managment

JAVA Basic HackerRank

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JAVA | SPRING BOOT | MAVEN | HIBERNATE
SQL | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS | DSA

SOFT SKILLS

Team Work | Problem Solving | Motivated

INTERESTS

Travelling | Hiking

EXPERIENCE

Store Manager

Mithi Mirchi Cafe 2019 – 2020 | Indore Worked as a Store Manager.

Sales Manager

DAYA WorldWide PVT. LTD. 2017 – 2019 | Indore Worked as a Sales Manager.

PROJECTS

Bus Reservation Rest_API

Rest_API using Spring Boot.

Tech-Stack

Java | SpringBoot | SQL | Hibernate | Swagger.

Responsibility

Feedback Section

Bewakoof Clone

Bewakoof is a lifestyle fashion brand that makes creative, distinctive fashion for the trendy, contemporary Indian.

Tech-Stack

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

Responsibility

Product Page Design | Sorting

Bath And Body Works Clone

Bath & Body Work is an online eCommerce cosmetic brand, Which is a retail store chain that sells soaps, lotions, fragrances, and candles. .

Tech-Stack

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

Responsibility

Team Lead | Layout of the website | Merging
